MacKaye Family papers ML-5
Rauner Special Collections Library
- Addendum 1, 1861-1953|; 22
  - Box: 218, 1861-1953 (Box 218)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Writing: Notes on "Shifting The Field Of Association", undated (Box 218, Folder 35)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Writing: Notes on "Socialism And Property", undated (Box 218, Folder 36)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Writing: Regarding Standard Oil Company, undated (Box 218, Folder 37)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Writing: Notes on "Standards Of Land Law", undated (Box 218, Folder 38)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Writing: "A Substitute For The Plumb Plan", undated (Box 218, Folder 39)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Writing: "Text Of New Theory Of Dynamic Universe, Displacing Relativity", 1930 (Box 218, Folder 40)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Writing: "The Theory Of Relativity: For What Is It A Disguise?", 1930 (Box 218, Folder 41)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Writing: Notes on Utilitarian Doctrine, undated (Box 218, Folder 42)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Writing: "Utility Project" Notes and Charts, undated (Box 218, Folder 43)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Writing: "What Socialism Is And Is Not" Fragment, undated (Box 218, Folder 44)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Writing: Unidentified MS, undated (Box 218, Folder 45)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Lecture Notes Dartmouth Philosophy Class 5, 1930 (Box 218, Folder 46)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Lecture Notes Dartmouth Philosophy Class 6, 1927 (Box 218, Folder 47)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Lecture Notes Dartmouth Philosophy Classes 53,54,63, 1930 (Box 218, Folder 48)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Lecture Notes Dartmouth Philosophy Classes Miscellaneous, undated (Box 218, Folder 49)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Lecture Notes "Lessons" #5,6,7,8,10, undated (Box 218, Folder 50)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Writing: "Political Engineering" MS, undated (Box 218, Folder 51)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Writing: Seminar 45, undated (Box 218, Folder 52)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Writing: Miscellaneous Unidentified Notes, undated (Box 218, Folder 53)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Writing: Miscellaneous Unidentified Notes, undated (Box 218, Folder 54)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Plate for: The Economy Of Happiness", undated (Box 218, Folder 55)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Writing: Regarding the Production of Wealth vs. Happiness, undated (Box 218, Folder 56)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Writing: "The Founder Of American Democracy", 1903 (Box 218, Folder 57)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Correspondence: To Peggy Morse MacKaye, 1909-1950 (Box 218, Folder 58)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Correspondence: To James Mackay From Family, 1878-1930 (Box 218, Folder 59)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Correspondence: Non-Family, 1902-1906 (Box 218, Folder 60)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Correspondence: Non-Family, 1907-1931 (Box 218, Folder 61)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Correspondence: William James, 1905-1908 (Box 218, Folder 62)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Correspondence: Horace Liveright, 1922-1926 (Box 218, Folder 63)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Correspondence: Maxwell Perkins, 1930 (Box 218, Folder 64)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Correspondence: Letters From James Medbery MacKaye, 1907-1933 (Box 218, Folder 65)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Correspondence: Letters About James Medbery MacKaye, 1920's (Box 218, Folder 66)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: About James, 1925-1930 (Box 218, Folder 67)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Book Reviews, 1906-1939 (Box 218, Folder 68)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: James' Contract with Scribners for "Dynamic Universe", 1930 (Box 218, Folder 69)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: James' Dartmouth Boys & Their Partners, 1937 (Box 218, Folder 70)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: James' Lectures, 1916-1932 (Box 218, Folder 71)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: James' Maps, 1886 (Box 218, Folder 72)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Miscellaneous, 1891-1953 (Box 218, Folder 73)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Regarding James Medbery MacKaye's Death, 1935 (Box 218, Folder 74)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Notebooks, 1861,1915 (Box 218, Folder 75)
  - Box: 219, 1862-1941 (Box 219)
    Box: 219
    - Steele MacKaye: Retuned Checks, 1878 (Box 219, Folder 1)
    - Steele MacKaye: Silk Program for "Paul Kavar", 1888 (Box 219, Folder 2)
    - Steele MacKaye: Facsimile of "Hamlet" Playbill, 1862 (Box 219, Folder 3)
    - Steele MacKaye: Regarding Steele's teaching at the Lyceum Theatre School, 1896 (Box 219, Folder 4)
    - Steele MacKaye: "The Innovation Of Steele MacKaye In Scenic Design And Stage Practices…" by David L. Guthrie, undated (Box 219, Folder 5)
    - Steele MacKaye: Writing: "Paul Kauvar" typescript, undated (Box 219, Folder 6)
    - Steele MacKaye: Writing: "Paul Kauvar" typscript, undated (Box 219, Folder 7)
    - Steele MacKaye: Writing: "Hazel Kirke" typscript, undated (Box 219, Folder 8)
    - Steele MacKaye: Writing: Miscellaneous, 1872-1933 (Box 219, Folder 9)
    - Steele MacKaye: About Steele, 1892-1931 (Box 219, Folder 10)
    - Steele MacKaye: Death of Steele MacKaye, 1894 (Box 219, Folder 11)
    - Steele MacKaye: Press Releases for Newspapers on the Spectatorium, 1893 (Box 219, Folder 12)
    - Steele MacKaye: Publicity Photos, undated (Box 219, Folder 13)
    - Steele MacKaye: Passports, 1871 (Box 219, Folder 14)
    - Steele MacKaye: Patent, undated (Box 219, Folder 15)
    - Steele MacKaye: Writing: Miscellaneous in English and French, undated (Box 219, Folder 16)
    - Steele MacKaye: Miscallaneous Notes of Scripts and Productions, undated (Box 219, Folder 17)
    - Steele MacKaye: Writing: "Philip Kirk" MS in French Two Acts, undated (Box 219, Folder 18)
    - Steele MacKaye: Writing: "Harold Wilkinson" Ms in French Onw Act, undated (Box 219, Folder 19)
    - Steele MacKaye: Writing: "Greymoor" MS Incomplete Script, undated (Box 219, Folder 20)
    - Steele MacKaye: Writing: Plot and Some Script of Unidentified Play possibly "The 50 Year Deadline", undated (Box 219, Folder 21)
    - Steele MacKaye: Writing: Various MSS of Acts and Rewrites of Play "Embers", 1876 (Box 219, Folder 22)
    - Steele MacKaye: Writing: "Won At Last" typscript, undated (Box 219, Folder 23)
    - Steele MacKaye: Writing: "The World-Finder" for the Spectatorium typscript fragments, 1892 (Box 219, Folder 24)
    - Steele MacKaye: Writing: "Condemned To Death MS, undated (Box 219, Folder 25)
    - Steele MacKaye: Writing: Plot of Play "Rooney's Departure"MS, undated (Box 219, Folder 26)
    - Steele MacKaye: Writing: "L'Ete De St. Martin" Play MS Fragments, undated (Box 219, Folder 27)
    - Steele MacKaye: Writing: Notebook, 1885 (Box 219, Folder 28)
    - Steele MacKaye: Writing: "Harmonic Gymnastics - Simple And Complex Expression And Stage Business" typescript, 1886 (Box 219, Folder 29)
    - Steele MacKaye: Miscellaneous Delsarte Notes, undated (Box 219, Folder 30)
    - Steele MacKaye: Delsarte Notes Possibly Written by Steele MacKaye, undated (Box 219, Folder 31)
    - Steele MacKaye: Delsarte "L'Art Oratoire" MS in French, undated (Box 219, Folder 32)
    - Steele MacKaye: Delsarte "D'Une Conference Faite A La Sorbonne" MS Fragments, 1866 (Box 219, Folder 33)
    - Steele MacKaye: Writing: Comments on "An Arrant Knave & Other Plays" by Steele MacKaye, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 34)
    - Steele MacKaye: Writing: "Safety In Theatres", 1882 (Box 219, Folder 35)
    - Steele MacKaye: Tickets for Hamlet, 1873 (Box 219, Folder 36)
    - Steele MacKaye: Writing: Souvenier Brochure for "The Henrietta" signed by Robson Crane, 1888 (Box 219, Folder 37)
    - Steele MacKaye: Sheet Music for "Hazel Kirk" Waltz, 1880 (Box 219, Folder 38)
    - Steele MacKaye: Writing: "Harmonic Gymnastics - Simple, amd Complex Expressions And Stage Business" with dedication to Will (brother), 1886 (Box 219, Folder 39)
    - Steele MacKaye: Photo of Castle of Buffalo, Home of Steele MacKaye, undated (Box 219, Folder 40)
  - Box: 220, 1840's-1940's (Box 220)
    Box: 220
    - Steele MacKaye: Sketches, 1878 (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - Steele MacKaye: Letters About Steele MacKaye, 1871 (Box 220, Folder 2)
    - Steele MacKaye: Letters to Steele MacKaye A-C, 1867-1894 (Box 220, Folder 3)
    - Steele MacKaye: Letters to Steele MacKaye D-L, 1876-1893 (Box 220, Folder 4)
    - Steele MacKaye: Letters to Steele MacKaye M-Q, 1874-1890 (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - Steele MacKaye: Letters to Steele MacKaye R-T, 1872-1894 (Box 220, Folder 6)
    - Steele MacKaye: Letters to Steele Mackay V-Z, 1878-1894 (Box 220, Folder 7)
    - Steele MacKaye: Letters to Steele Mackay from F.A. Durivage, 1870-1871 (Box 220, Folder 8)
    - Steele MacKaye: Correspondence with Tom Taylor, 1870's (Box 220, Folder 9)
    - Steele MacKaye: Correspondence with Emily MacKaye von Hesse, 1872-1893 (Box 220, Folder 10)
    - Steele MacKaye: Correspondence with Col. James MacKaye, 1866-1871 (Box 220, Folder 11)
    - Steele MacKaye: Correspondence Family, 1873-1890 (Box 220, Folder 12)
    - Steele MacKaye: Letters from Steele Mackay, 1874-1893 (Box 220, Folder 13)
    - Steele MacKaye: Regarding Steele MacKaye's Death, 1894 (Box 220, Folder 14)
    - Steele MacKaye: Copies of Letters from Del Sarte, 1870-1871 (Box 220, Folder 15)
    - Steele MacKaye: Miscellaneous, 1873-1887 (Box 220, Folder 16)
    - Steele MacKaye: Centenary, 1942 (Box 220, Folder 17)
    - Steele MacKaye: Notebooks, 1880's (Box 220, Folder 18)
    - Steele MacKaye: Notebooks, undated (Box 220, Folder 19)
    - Harold MacKaye: "The Miner 87", 1887 (Box 220, Folder 20)
    - Harold MacKaye: School Notebook, undated (Box 220, Folder 21)
    - Harold MacKaye: Letters to Harold MacKaye, 1877-1894 (Box 220, Folder 22)
    - Harold MacKaye: Correspondence to Will Makcaye, 1910 (Box 220, Folder 23)
    - Harold MacKaye: Writings, 1893-1931 (Box 220, Folder 24)
    - James Knowles Medbery: Obituary and Portrait, undated (Box 220, Folder 25)
    - James Knowles Medbery: Miscellaneous Poetry, undated (Box 220, Folder 26)
    - James Knowles Medbery: Diary Entries, 1856-1859 (Box 220, Folder 27)
    - James Knowles Medbery: Writing "The College Today" and "The Secret-Society Man", undated (Box 220, Folder 28)
    - James Knowles Medbery: Writing "About The Revolution/General Howe", undated (Box 220, Folder 29)
    - James Knowles Medbery: Writing "Speech Of Mr. hacket In The Senate…", undated (Box 220, Folder 30)
    - James Knowles Medbery: Writing "Story About Joe Bainey", undated (Box 220, Folder 31)
    - James Knowles Medbery: Writings in Greek, undated (Box 220, Folder 32)
    - James Knowles Medbery: Book I - Chapter I on Heliogabolus, undated (Box 220, Folder 33)
    - James Knowles Medbery: Notes on Capital Punishment, undated (Box 220, Folder 34)
    - James Knowles Medbery: Notes and News Clippings on Railroad Monopolies in New Jersey, 1860's (Box 220, Folder 35)
    - Helen Lane MacKaye: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1894-1933 (Box 220, Folder 36)
    - David Loring Makcaye: Miscellaneous, 1941-1945 (Box 220, Folder 37)
    - James Stewart MacKaye: Newspaper Clippings of Wedding and Son's Birth, 1941 (Box 220, Folder 38)
    - William Payson MacKaye Jr.: Sketch and Writing, 1938, 1942 (Box 220, Folder 39)
    - Col. James MacKaye: Letter, 1850 (Box 220, Folder 40)
    - William MacKaye: Letters, 1886-1889 (Box 220, Folder 41)
    - William MacKaye: Miscellaneous, 1880-1888 (Box 220, Folder 42)
    - Sarah MacKaye Warner: Miscellaneous Letters, 1870's (Box 220, Folder 43)
    - Lucy Ann Steele Faxon: Correspondence with Sarah Loring MacKaye Warner, 1860's -1870's (Box 220, Folder 44)
    - Emily Benton Steele MacKaye: Correspondence with Lucy Ann Steele Faxon, 1844 (Box 220, Folder 45)
    - Rev. Nicholas Medbery: Letter and Miscellaneous, 1870's (Box 220, Folder 46)
    - Rebecca Belknap Stetson Medbery: Letters and Miscellaneous, 1840's (Box 220, Folder 47)
    - Mary Medbery MacKaye: Correspondence with James Knowles Medbery, circ 1860's (Box 220, Folder 48)
    - Program from Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show, undated (Box 220, Folder 49)
    - Program from Christmas Show put on by MacKaye Children, 1878 (Box 220, Folder 50)
    - News Clippings Aboutt MacKaye Family, 1889 (Box 220, Folder 51)
    - Anonomous Play by One of the MacKaye Boys, undated (Box 220, Folder 52)
    - Arthur Loring MacKaye: Letter and Envelopes, 1873 (Box 220, Folder 53)
  - Box: 221, 1852-1945, 1973 (Box 221)
    Box: 221
    - Newspaper Clipping Photo of Arvia and Christy MacKaye, undated (Box 221, Folder 1)
    - Arvia MacKaye: Letters to Arvia, 1911-1921 (Box 221, Folder 2)
    - Arvia MacKaye: Letters from Arvia to Others, 1901-1911 (Box 221, Folder 3)
    - Arvia MacKaye: Writings, 1912-1921 (Box 221, Folder 4)
    - Arvia MacKaye: Linoleum Prints (oversized) and Miscellaneous Sketches, undated (Box 221, Folder 5)
    - Arvia MacKaye: Sketches and Miscelleneous, 1910-1920's (Box 221, Folder 6)
    - Karl Ege: Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 221, Folder 7)
    - Christy MacKaye: Correspondence with Family, 1909-1932 (Box 221, Folder 8)
    - Christy MacKaye: Correspondence Non-Family, 1909,1935 (Box 221, Folder 9)
    - Christy MacKaye: Childhood Writings, 1920's (Box 221, Folder 10)
    - Christy MacKaye: Miscelleneous, 1922-1942 (Box 221, Folder 11)
    - Henry Barnes: Pamphlet "Education As Art", 1950 (Box 221, Folder 12)
    - Robert MacKaye: Correspondence from Family, 1910-1921 (Box 221, Folder 13)
    - Robert MacKaye: Correspondence Non-Family, 1918-1922 (Box 221, Folder 14)
    - Robert MacKaye: Correspondence from Robert MacKaye, 1907,1922 (Box 221, Folder 15)
    - Robert MacKaye: Miscellaneous, 1910-1927 (Box 221, Folder 16)
    - Robert MacKaye: Sketches, undated (Box 221, Folder 17)
    - Robert MacKaye: Writings, 1920's-1950 (Box 221, Folder 18)
    - Arvia MacKaye: Linoleum Block for Prints, undated (Box 221, Folder 19)
    - Arvia MacKaye: Book: "Voyage To The Other Land" by Albert Steffen translated by Arvia, 1939 (Box 221, Folder 20)
    - Christy MacKaye: Bound Poems "Horizon" by Christy MacKaye, 1940 (Box 221, Folder 21)
    - Bound Scrapbook of Chidren's Drawings and Clippings, undated (Box 221, Folder 22)
    - Miscallenous Letters not from Mrs. MacKaye, 1887-1892 (Box 221, Folder 23)
    - Mary Ellen Keith Medbery MacKaye: Childhood Letters, 1852 (Box 221, Folder 24)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: First Childhood Scrapbook, 1877 (Box 221, Folder 25)
    - Child's Notebook, undated (Box 221, Folder 26)
    - Child's Small Slate Blackboard, undated (Box 221, Folder 27)
    - Children's Miscellaneous, undated (Box 221, Folder 28)
    - Children's Drawings and Letters, undated (Box 221, Folder 29)
    - Arthur Loring MacKaye: Childhood Letters and Drawing, 1870's (Box 221, Folder 30)
    - Harold MacKaye: Childhood Letters and Drawings, 1870's (Box 221, Folder 31)
    - William MacKaye: Childhood Letters and Drawings, 1870's (Box 221, Folder 32)
    - James Medbery MacKaye: Childhood Letters and Drawings, 1879 (Box 221, Folder 33)
    - Percy MacKaye: Childhood Letters and Drawings, undated (Box 221, Folder 34)
    - Benton MacKaye: Childhood Letters and Drawings, 1880's (Box 221, Folder 35)
    - Hazel MacKaye: Childhood Letters and Drawings, undated (Box 221, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous Letters and Drawings by MacKaye Children, 1920's (Box 221, Folder 37)
    - Hazel MacKaye: Writings, undated (Box 221, Folder 38)
    - Hazel MacKaye: Notes from Diary, undated (Box 221, Folder 39)
    - Hazel MacKaye: Diary, 1909 (Box 221, Folder 40)
    - Hazel MacKaye: "America's Men And Women" Men's League Suffrage Pageant, 1914 (Box 221, Folder 41)
    - Hazel MacKaye: Treatment of "Brer Rabbit", undated (Box 221, Folder 42)
    - Hazel MacKaye: Treatment of "Cyrano de Bergerac", undated (Box 221, Folder 43)
  - Box: 222, 1850's-1920's, 1971, 1973 (Box 222)
    Box: 222
    - Hazel MacKaye: Writing: "The Enchated Pool", undated (Box 222, Folder 1)
    - Hazel MacKaye: Writing: "The Enchanted Urn", 1919 (Box 222, Folder 2)
    - Hazel MacKaye: Writing: "Enchantment/Mars And The Maiden", undated (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - Hazel MacKaye: Writing: "Euclid In Wood" A One Act Play, 1932 (Box 222, Folder 4)
    - Hazel MacKaye: Writing: "Feathers and Fantasy", undated (Box 222, Folder 5)
    - Hazel MacKaye: Writing: "A Day In Baby's Life" US Department of Labor Film, 1915 (Box 222, Folder 6)
    - Hazel MacKaye: Writing: Untitled, undated (Box 222, Folder 7)
    - Hazel MacKaye: Writing: "When Willie Went To Work", undated (Box 222, Folder 8)
    - Hazel MacKaye: Writing: "When Tom Went To Work", undated (Box 222, Folder 9)
    - Hazel MacKaye: Writing: "Forward into Light" Inez Milholland Memorial Pageant, undated (Box 222, Folder 10)
    - Hazel MacKaye: Writing: "Garden Of The Gods" 75th Anniversary of first Equal Rights Meeting, 1923 (Box 222, Folder 11)
    - Hazel MacKaye: Writing: Girl Reserves Pageant, undated (Box 222, Folder 12)
    - Hazel MacKaye: Writing: "Good Will, The Magician" Children's Peace Play, undated (Box 222, Folder 13)
    - Hazel MacKaye: Writing: "The History Of Liberalism In Religion" A Pageant, 1921 (Box 222, Folder 14)
    - Percy MacKaye: "Various Verses 1890-1897" Bound (Box 222, Folder 15)
    - Percy MacKaye: "Marion's Ring Rhymes and Arvia's Garden" Poems Bound, 1898-1900 (Box 222, Folder 16)
    - Percy MacKaye: "L'Epou Vantail - The Scarecrow" Bound, undated (Box 222, Folder 17)
    - Benton MacKaye: Correspondence, 1971 (Box 222, Folder 18)
    - Percy MacKaye: Sketches and Notes for "The Scarecrow", undated (Box 222, Folder 19)
    - Percy MacKaye: Program and Photos for "Sactuary - A Bird Masque", 1913 (Box 222, Folder 20)
    - Photographs, Portraits and Others, some dry-mounted, undated (Box 222, Folder 21)
    - Benton MacKaye: Audiotaped Interview, 1973 (Box 222, Folder 22)
    - Oil and Watercolor Paintings of Landscapes, undated (Box 222, Folder 23)
    - Wedding-, Anniversary-, and Other Invitations to Various Members of MacKaye Family, 1850's-1910 (Box 222, Folder 25)
    - Various Bills and Receipts, 1902-1920 (Box 222, Folder 27)
    - Hazel MacKaye: Miscellaneous Ephemera, 1890's (Box 222, Folder 24)
    - Various Bills and Receipts, 1870's-1912 (Box 222, Folder 26)
  - Contains Photographs: Primarily Portraits of Actors, Actresses and Children; Some Landscapes, an..., 1880's-1950's (Box 223)
    Contains Photographs: Primarily Portraits of Actors, Actresses and Children; Some Landscapes, and Pageant Photos, Non-Family
  - Box: 224, 1880's-1960's (Box 224)
    Box: 224
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 224, Folder 1)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Family Reunion, 1916 (Box 224, Folder 2)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Arthur MacKaye, 1890's (Box 224, Folder 3)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Arthur MacKaye and Helen MacKaye, 1930 (Box 224, Folder 4)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Arvia MacKaye as a Child, undated (Box 224, Folder 5)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Aunt Sadie, undated (Box 224, Folder 6)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Benton MacKaye, undated (Box 224, Folder 7)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Bonniecroft - Hal and Helen's Home, undated (Box 224, Folder 8)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Christy MacKaye and Family, 1929-1960 (Box 224, Folder 9)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Harold MacKaye and Helen MacKaye, 1866-1938 (Box 224, Folder 10)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Hazel MacKaye, undated (Box 224, Folder 11)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Hazel MacKaye, undated (Box 224, Folder 12)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: James MacKaye, 1912-1941 (Box 224, Folder 13)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Col. James Morrison MacKaye, undated (Box 224, Folder 14)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Loring MacKaye, 1891-19661 (Box 224, Folder 15)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Marion MacKaye, 1898, 1943 (Box 224, Folder 16)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Mary MacKaye Weis, 1932-1959 (Box 224, Folder 17)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Mary Medbery MacKaye, 1845-1910 (Box 224, Folder 18)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Percy MacKaye, 1897-1942 (Box 224, Folder 19)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Percy MacKaye, 1895-1942 (Box 224, Folder 20)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Robert Keith MacKaye, 1900-1916 (Box 224, Folder 21)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Sarah Loring MacKaye, undated (Box 224, Folder 22)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Steele MacKaye Stage Photographs, undated (Box 224, Folder 23)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Steele MacKaye Stage Photographs, undated (Box 224, Folder 24)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: William MacKaye, 1887-1905 (Box 224, Folder 25)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: William Payson MacKaye and Katy, 1897-1962 (Box 224, Folder 26)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: William Payson MacKaye Jr. and Family, undate (Box 224, Folder 27)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: James Stewart MacKaye, 1920, 1943-1944 (Box 224, Folder 28)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: James Stewart MacKaye Jr. and Family, 1943-1960 (Box 224, Folder 29)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Jean MacKaye Colby and Family, 1950-1956 (Box 224, Folder 30)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Mary MacKaye Wertheimer and Family, 1952-1963 (Box 224, Folder 31)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Old Tin-Type Benton MacKaye, Percy, Mrs. MacKaye with Hazel on lap, 1889 (Box 224, Folder 32)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Shirley Homstead, 1920's (Box 224, Folder 33)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Elise and Edward Hudson, undated (Box 224, Folder 34)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: James Knowles Medbery, undated (Box 224, Folder 35)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Rebecca Stetson Medbery, undated (Box 224, Folder 36)
    - Photographs MacKaye Family: Photographs of People Related to the MacKayes, undated (Box 224, Folder 37)
    - MacKaye Family: Printed Sketches, undated (Box 224, Folder 38)
  - Contains Photographs of the MacKaye Family; Journals, "The Congregationalist" and "The Christian..., 1880's -1920's (Box 225)
    Contains Photographs of the MacKaye Family; Journals, "The Congregationalist" and "The Christian World Journal", and Knitted Slippers
  - Box: 226, 1886-1922 (Box 226)
    Box: 226
    - Jesse Bell Hardy MacKaye: Bills and Receipts, 1917-1920 (Box 226, Folder 1)
    - Jesse Bell Hardy MacKaye: Checkbook, 1919-1920 (Box 226, Folder 2)
    - Jesse Bell Hardy MacKaye: Checkbook, 1921 (Box 226, Folder 3)
    - Jesse Bell Hardy MacKaye: Cancelled Checks and Records, 1921-1922 (Box 226, Folder 4)
    - Jesse Bell Hardy MacKaye: Savings Account Passbooks, 1916, 1919 (Box 226, Folder 5)
    - Jesse Bell Hardy MacKaye: News Clippings, undated (Box 226, Folder 6)
    - Jesse Bell Hardy MacKaye: Personal News Clippings, 1915 (Box 226, Folder 7)
    - Jesse Bell Hardy MacKaye: News Clippings About Jesse Belll Hardy MacKaye, 1915-1921 (Box 226, Folder 8)
    - Jesse Bell Hardy MacKaye: Clipping Book, 1913-195 (Box 226, Folder 9)
    - Jesse Bell Hardy MacKaye: News Clippings, 1915-1916 (Box 226, Folder 10)
    - Jesse Bell Hardy MacKaye: Clipping Book, 1916 (Box 226, Folder 11)
    - Jesse Bell Hardy MacKaye: Clipping Book, 1919 (Box 226, Folder 12)
    - Jesse Bell Hardy MacKaye: Clipping Book - Lawrence-Hertzka Meeting, 1920 (Box 226, Folder 13)
    - Jesse Bell Hardy MacKaye: Amnesty Material, 1920 (Box 226, Folder 14)
    - Jesse Bell Hardy MacKaye: Appointment Calendars, 1921 (Box 226, Folder 15)
    - Jesse Bell Hardy MacKaye: Autograph Book, 1886 (Box 226, Folder 16)
    - Jesse Bell Hardy MacKaye: Writing: "Beatiude", undated (Box 226, Folder 17)
    - Jesse Bell Hardy MacKaye: Marriage Certiicate to Benton MacKaye, 1915 (Box 226, Folder 18)
    - Jesse Bell Hardy MacKaye: Birth Control Material, 1918-1921 (Box 226, Folder 19)
    - Jesse Bell Hardy MacKaye: Booklet by Benton MacKaye, 1922 (Box 226, Folder 20)
    - Jesse Bell Hardy MacKaye: Christmas Card, 1921 (Box 226, Folder 21)